radware.com 2019-06-30

# Website Privacy Policy

#### What are you looking for?

Radware Ltd. and its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Radware”) respects the privacy of the users of this Website. This Privacy Policy outlines the steps Radware is taking to protect users' privacy and the limitations in doing so.

By registering at our site, logging in, or by any other method of voluntarily providing Radware with your personal information, you accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and provide your consent for its use.

**Collection of Personal Information**. Personal information may be collected in one of three ways: (i) Users may submit personal information (such as name, email address, telephone number) while using this Website for the purpose of registering and logging into the Website, downloading software or information, applying for a job, requesting information and other uses; (ii) when entering a product serial number, the Website will be updated with the applicable customer information. Information referred to under sections (i) and (ii) shall be referred to herein as "Personal Information" and the information referred to under section (iii) shall be referred to herein as "Tracking Information".

**Use of Personal Information.** Personal Information is not used or provided to any third party, except as outlined herein. By logging into our Website and/or by providing your Personal Information, Radware assumes you are interested in obtaining more information about our company, its technology and our product offerings or job opportunities. Therefore, Radware may use your Personal Information solely for the purpose of (i) providing you with products, services, upgrades and additional offerings available on our Website; (ii) providing you with information Radware believes you would be interested in, such as newsletters, product updates, special offers, campaigns, service renewals and additional promotional materials; or (iii) answering your questions and inquiries. Radware may also provide your contact information to Radware’s affiliates, business partners or other third parties acting on its behalf in order to (i) provide you with Radware’s products and services or provide joint or bundled solutions; or (ii) provide you with joint offers and complementary information which Radware believes may be of interest to you.

**Use of Tracking Information.** Tracking Information is used solely for statistical, web performance and analysis with the aim of improving the efficiency and performance of our Website. Radware does not provide the Tracking Information to any third party and do not use it for any purpose other than as stated herein. Radware may use standard technologies, such as cookies and other HTML tools, to collect information about how you use the Website or to record that you opened an email marketing message, solely for analysis purposes.

**Help US Keep Accurate Information.** Radware understands the importance of maintaining accurate records. Please help keep your records accurate by contacting Radware with any changes or corrections to your information at [datasubjectrights@radware.com](mailto:datasubjectrights@radware.com).

**You May Request the Modification or Removal of your Personal Information.** You may request to modify your Personal Information or ask not to receive additional offers and information at any time by contacting [datasubjectrights@radware.com](mailto:datasubjectrights@radware.com).

Radware supports your "Right to be forgotten". You may request to remove your Personal Information at any time by contacting [datasubjectrights@radware.com](mailto:datasubjectrights@Radware.com).

**Links to Third-party Websites**. This Website may contain links to third-party websites. Radware is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites.

**Security of Your Information**. Radware, as a provider of world class security products, takes the security of your personal information as a top priority. Radware encrypts your information when it is transported or stored. Access is restricted to Radware staff members with a need to know. Radware monitors its technology platforms to protect against unauthorized access to your information.

**Cross-Border Transfer, Processing and Storage of Personal Information**. As a global organization, Radware may transfer your personal information to Radware in Israel, to any Radware’s affiliates worldwide, or to its business partners or other third parties in Israel or worldwide acting on its behalf, for the purposes of processing or storage of the personal information pursuant to this Policy.

**Children's Privacy**. Radware is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. Radware does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 16 and Radware does not target its Website to children under 16.

**Disclosure of Information as Required by Law**. Radware may be forced to disclose Tracking Information or Personal information if required to do so by applicable law or by a competent governmental or judicial order to prevent any illegal or harmful activities.

**Data Retention**. Radware keeps your personal information only so long as Radware needs it to provide the products or services you requested, fulfill all the other purposes described in this Policy, and for other essential purposes such as complying with Radware’s legal obligations, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, maintaining security, detecting and preventing fraud and abuse, enforce our agreements and comply with all applicable laws. This is also the case for anyone that Radware shares your personal information with and who carries out services on Radware’s behalf. Retention periods can vary significantly based on the type of information and how it is used. Radware’s retention periods are based on criteria that include legally mandated retention periods, pending or potential litigation, our intellectual property or ownership rights, contract requirements, operational directives or needs, and historical archiving. When Radware no longer needs to use your personal information and there is no need for Radware to keep it to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, we’ll either remove it from our systems or depersonalize it so that we can't identify you.

**Disclosure of Information as a Result of Reorganization**. Radware may also be forced to disclose Tracking Information or Personal Information as part of a corporate reorganization, restructuring or merger activities, to the extent required to consummate such activities.

**Amendment of Policy**. Radware reserves the right to amend the terms of this Policy from time to time without notice, by posting the revised terms on the Website.

**Questions**. You may contact Radware with any questions regarding our Privacy Policy at [DPO@radware.com](mailto:DPO@radware.com).

**COPYRIGHT © 2018, Radware Ltd. All Rights Reserved.**

#### Contact Radware Sales

Assess your needs and understand which products are best

Contact Us Now
